(Leonard:)Okay.
(Amy:)I suppose being
the first people
(Amy:)on a new planet would
be incredibly exciting.
(Sheldon(on video):)Oh, I know.
(Sheldon:)We could be the first
to plant a flag on Mars.
(Sheldon:)We could be the first to
watch Mars Attacks! on Mars.
(Sheldon:)We could be the first
to say "Good Lord,
(Sheldon:)what on Mars are
you talking about?"
(Sheldon:)You know,
(Amy:)we could also be
the first people
(Amy:)to procreate on Mars.
(Sheldon:)You just can't keep it in
your space pants, can you?
(Amy:)Think about it.
(Amy:)If we had a family there,
(Amy:)our kids would be Martians.
(Sheldon:)They would, wouldn't they?
(Sheldon:)We could give them
cool Martian names.
(Sheldon:)And we could teach them
about Martian history.
(Sheldon:)Like, who planted those flags?
(Sheldon:)And, uh, where did that copy
of Mars Attacks! come from?
(Amy:)I guess we'll have to make
(Amy:)a new video together,
as a couple.